redirectmenow.com 2009-06-17

# DesktopSmiley.com - Desktop Smiley with 10,000 Free emoticons and Smileys for your E-mail, IM, Blog, Profiles and more!

DESKTOP SMILEY PRIVACY POLICY

DoubleD Advertising Limited is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains how DoubleD Advertising Networks collects and utilizes your personal information when you use our products and services, including consumer software, such as the Desktop Smiley Toolbar 

WHY DO WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?

DoubleD Advertising - Desktop Smiley collects personal information to improve the manner by which we operate and offer our products and services, communicate with you about those products and services, and provide effective, timely customer support when needed. We will never rent or sell any of the personally-identifiable information we collect from you to third parties, and will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties without your consent, unless such sharing is necessary for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

Information gathered during the registration or account creation process, or during installation to particular products, may differ based on the nature of the product or service. Information that you provide when registering, or accessing to the IM products or services, may include: name and email address; information concerning software downloaded, products and content accessed; location information (such as zip code or postal code and country); computer configuration (such as operating system, connection speed, and peripherals); the IP Internet (IP) address and URL of the Website that sent you to the Desktop Smiley page; demographic information provided by you (such as language, gender and age, and, if applicable, content preferences and personalization information); email accounts login name and password; and searched keywords history through Desktop Smiley Toolbar search boxes.

We will not sell, rent or otherwise distribute your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent, except as set forth below. 

HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE?

DoubleD Advertising understands that it is a privilege to have you as a customer and is committed to protecting your personal information. We use the following controls to protect your personal information:

  * Use of secure connections using SSL to safeguard information when transmitted from your Web browser to Desktop Smiley servers;
  * Use of security controls to restrict access to databases housing personally identifying information;
  * Use of encryption for sensitive personal information, such as email accounts login name and password
  * Restrict employee access to databases containing personal information and impose confidentiality requirements upon employees who do; and
  * Bind subcontractors with contractual, technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information.

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

DoubleD Advertising - Desktop Smiley uses your personal information to:

  * Deliver to you for DoubleD Advertising - Desktop Smiley products and services, and communicate with you concerning customer service issues;
  * Improve our software and services by providing personalized content recommendations, language and location customization, and/or personalized help and dedicated personalized content;
  * Determine if you meet the minimum system requirements to use our products, and provide information concerning compatibility and interoperability to you;
  * Ask you to participate in surveys about products, services, news and events;
  * Offer you product upgrades, content, services and games for you to purchase;
  * Provide you with content, services, instructions, and a more personalized experience based on personal information, such as zip/postal code, country locations, and any content or other preferences you provide;
  * Auto-update downloaded Desktop Smiley products;
  * Provide you with news, free newsletters, updates, targeted advertising, promotions, and special offers; and
  * Better understand how our products are used, including Web traffic patterns, Search patterns and what types of content are most popular with users of our products and services.

WHEN AND HOW DO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES?

DoubleD Advertising - Desktop Smiley does not use your personal information for purposes incompatible with those listed above. Desktop Smiley does not sell, rent, or share your personal information to a third party unless you consent to provide such information to a third party partner or content service.

In some cases, access to certain products and services, such as content subscription products or products distributed by third parties, may require the provision of personal information to a third party, such as a content provider, offer co-registration or distributor. In such cases, this will be stated during the registration process, in the terms of use, through the distribution process, or in a similar manner. The third party's use of such information is governed by that party's privacy policy, and Desktop Smiley use is governed by this privacy policy. Please visit the privacy policy of the content partner to make sure you understand how they use the personal information you provide to them. If you do not wish for such a transfer to take place, you should not register for the applicable product or service. Additionally, Desktop Smiley may be required to provide specific access and usage information to certain content providers and rights holders as a condition of content licensing and royalties. In such cases, Desktop Smiley may provide content usage, access, demographic and other information without your personally identifiable information (your name, billing information, email address) to the content provider.

Desktop Smiley may disclose relevant information about our customers to our contractors (e.g. a customer service contractor) in order for them to provide specific services for Desktop Smiley, and to better serve our customers. Desktop Smiley's contractors are bound by strict contractual requirements to keep all personal information they process strictly confidential and to use such information solely on behalf of Desktop Smiley.

Also, Desktop Smiley may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law; (b) comply with the order of a competent judicial authority in any jurisdiction; (c) comply with legal process served on DoubleD Advertising Limited; (d) protect and defend the rights or property of DoubleD Advertising Limited; or (e) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of DoubleD Advertising Limited?Desktop Smiley products or the public at large.

Desktop Smiley Websites and products contain links to other Websites and products. Desktop Smiley is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites or products. Please visit the privacy policies of these third party sites in order to understand their privacy policies and data collection practices. 

Obligatory or Optional Nature of the Requested Information

Some of the personal information collected by Desktop Smiley is necessary to provide you with the DESKTOP SMILEY product or service you choose and to optimize the delivery of data to your computer. DESKTOP SMILEY software may include the opportunity to disable certain software features to increase your level of privacy. However, certain technical information (e.g., zip code, product id, GUID) may be automatically transmitted between networked servers to authenticate access to products and services, enable their delivery, user verification tracking or optimize your data delivery experience. 

E-MAIL FROM Desktop Smiley

Registering for a product or service allows you to tell us how or whether you want Desktop Smiley to communicate with you. Generally, we send e-mail to you about our products, content and special offers. Separate DESKTOP SMILEY products, services and lines of business may send separate newsletters and marketing emails. During registration, you may opt out of receiving Desktop Smiley marketing e-mails and/or newsletters for the relevant product or service. Additionally, you may changed the preference for receiving such marketing emails at the Option setting within the Products. However, we may continue to send you e-mail about products or services you have previously purchased, or to inform you about critical technical service issues relating to a Desktop Smiley product or service. 

HOW TO ACCESS AND UPDATE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

To access your information and preferences, select "Edit Profile" from the menus on either the Desktop Smiley Toolbar (in most versions of the Toolbar, under the "Option" menu) and modify your information and preferences as needed.

You can also manage your preferences concerning receipt of newsletters and promotional emails. 

SECURITY OF PERSONAL USE OF COOKIES

Like other major Websites, we use cookies to provide you with a tailored experience when visiting our Websites and using our products. We also use cookies to understand traffic patterns on Desktop Smiley Websites and to trace users origin for affiliation marketing purpose. We treat any personal information that may be contained in cookies with the same level of confidentiality as other information you provide to us.

Desktop Smiley does not require that you accept cookies, however, some functionality on our Websites and products and services may be disabled if you decline to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. 

CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We frequently revise this Privacy Policy to keep it up to date with DESKTOP SMILEY products, services and Web pages. "Updated" may be used to alert users to recent changes and to the date of the last update. We also post FAQ's from time to time on specific products. 

NON-US CUSTOMER INFORMATION

If you are a customer who is from outside the United States, the personal information you submit to Desktop Smiley will be sent to and stored in servers in our headquarters in HONG KONG. The personal information practices set out in this Privacy Policy apply to all DoubleD Advertising Limited - Desktop Smiley customers worldwide.

For other data privacy questions, please contact/send an email to [privacypolicy@desktopsmiley.com](mailto:privacypolicy@desktopsmiley.com). 

NO ERROR FREE PERFORMANCE

We customarily release alpha and beta versions of our products, which are further refined before the release of the final version. Because these products are still in a test phase, we may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. As such, we welcome feedback on any privacy concerns you may have, and on how to improve our products generally, in all stages of release. Desktop Smiley does not guarantee error-free performance under this privacy policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this privacy policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with our privacy policy. Desktop Smiley shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of Hong Kong. 

CONTACT US ABOUT PRIVACY

If you have questions about the privacy aspects of our products or services or would like to make a complaint, please contact: [privacypolicy@desktopsmiley.com](mailto:privacypolicy@desktopsmiley.com) or Advertising Ltd. 201-203 Castle Peak Road, Cheung Sha Wan, Hong Kong.
